const essentialsChapter17QuizData = [
  {
    id: "17_1",
    question: "A(n) _________ is a venting heated system of predominantly masonry construction having a mass of at least 1760 pounds, excluding the chimney and base. (Page 215)",
    options: ["Freestanding Stove", "Masonry Heater", "Wood Insert", "Open Fireplace"],
    answer: "Masonry Heater"
  },
  {
    id: "17_2",
    question: "A Masonry Heaters is similar to a Factory-Built Fireplace, meaning it is usually built in a factory. (Page 215)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "17_3",
    question: "Clearances to combustibles under ASTM E1602 are at least _________ at the sides and rear. (Page 215)",
    options: ["4 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches", "8 inches"],
    answer: "4 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "17_4",
    question: "Clearances to combustibles under ASTM E1602 are at least _________ above. (Page 215)",
    options: ["4 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches", "8 inches"],
    answer: "8 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "17_5",
    question: "When it comes to Masonry Heaters, with a raised hearth, floor protection or heart extension should extend at least _________ in front of the loading door if the hearth or floor protection is 8 inches or above the floor level. (Page 216)",
    options: ["20 inches", "18 inches", "16 inches", "8 inches"],
    answer: "16 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "17_6",
    question: "When it comes to Masonry Heaters, with a raised hearth, floor protection or heart extension should extend at least _________ in front of the loading door if the hearth or floor protection is less than 8 inches above the floor level. (Page 216)",
    options: ["20 inches", "18 inches", "16 inches", "8 inches"],
    answer: "20 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "17_7",
    question: "Masonry chimneys are rarely built on top of the masonry heater, but alongside instead. (Page 216)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_8",
    question: "In masonry heater design, smoke travels from the firebox to the chimney through _________. (Page 216)",
    options: ["Fan Assisted Draft", "Heat Exchange Channels", "Catalytic Combustor", "Barometric Damper"],
    answer: "Heat Exchange Channels"
  },
  {
    id: "17_9",
    question: "Because of potential negative air pressurization issues, many jurisdictions require a dedicated outside combustion air supply to be vented near the loading door or to the interior of the heaters. (Page 216)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_10",
    question: "Sometimes, Masonry Heaters may have integral bake ovens built into them. (Page 217)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_11",
    question: "Masonry Heaters are designed to be fired usually no more than once or twice a day with rapid and hot fires. (Page 217)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_12",
    question: "With Masonry HEaters, the heat from the fire is transmitted through smoke channels to the masonry mass and radiated to the heated space for many hours after the fire is out. (Page 217)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_13",
    question: "Sweeping Masonry Heaters is normally needed less often because they burn very clean. (Page 218)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_14",
    question: "When inspecting the firebox on a masonry heater, when is it not problematic if you see cracking? (Page 218)",
    options: ["If the cracking is not structural", "The smoke channels are cracked", "The door is cracked", "The main outside of the firebox is cracked"],
    answer: "If the cracking is not structural"
  },
  {
    id: "17_15",
    question: "Masonry Heaters can only be vented into _________. (Page 219)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Chimneys conforming to UL 103HT", "Masonry Chimneys", "Single Wall Pipe", "Factory-Built Chimneys conforming to UL 103"],
    answer: "Factory-Built Chimneys conforming to UL 103HT"
  },
  {
    id: "17_16",
    question: "When removing smoke channel access covers on a masonry heater, they should go back to their original location, so you should number them before hand. (Page 220)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "17_17",
    question: "Every time you sweep a chimney a _________ is required. (Page 221)",
    options: ["Level I", "Level II", "Level III", "Category II"],
    answer: "Level I"
  },
];


if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 17: Sweeping Masonry Heaters'] = essentialsChapter17QuizData;
